uwcblog.com 2010-01-02

# Privacy Policy « UWC Blog Network | Free Blogging Software

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Universal Wealth Creation we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our blogging products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

**Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:**

Creative Commons License (Note, we’ve decided to make the below Privacy Policy available under a Creative Commons Sharealike license, which means you’re more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use, just make sure to replace references to us with ones to you, and if you want we’d appreciate a link to UWCBlog.com somewhere on your site.)

Universal Wealth Creation Pty Ltd. (“Universal Wealth Creation”) operates several websites including UniversalWealthCreation.com, UWCBlog.com and others. It is Universal Wealth Creation’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Universal Wealth Creation collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Universal Wealth Creation’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Universal Wealth Creation’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Universal Wealth Creation may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Universal Wealth Creation also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Universal Wealth Creation does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Universal Wealth Creation’s websites choose to interact with Universal Wealth Creation in ways that require Universal Wealth Creation to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Universal Wealth Creation gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for a blog at UWCBlog.com to provide a username and email address. Universal Wealth Creation collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Universal Wealth Creation. Universal Wealth Creation does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Universal Wealth Creation may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Universal Wealth Creation may monitor the most popular blogs on the UWCBlog.com site or use spam screened by the Akismet service to help identify spam. Universal Wealth Creation may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Universal Wealth Creation does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.  
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Universal Wealth Creation discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Universal Wealth Creation’s behalf or to provide services available at Universal Wealth Creation’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Universal Wealth Creation’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Universal Wealth Creation will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Universal Wealth Creation discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Universal Wealth Creation believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Universal Wealth Creation, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Universal Wealth Creation website and have supplied your email address, Universal Wealth Creation may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Universal Wealth Creation and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Universal Wealth Creation takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Universal Wealth Creation uses cookies to help Universal Wealth Creation identify and track visitors, their usage of Universal Wealth Creation website, and their website access preferences. Universal Wealth Creation visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Universal Wealth Creation’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Universal Wealth Creation’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Universal Wealth Creation may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Universal Wealth Creation’s sole discretion. Universal Wealth Creation encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a UWCBlog.com account, you should also check your blog’s dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
